fileden.com 2010-06-12

# FileDen.com | Free file hosting and online storage

**Overview**  
This privacy policy applies to the use of File Den (http://www.fileden.com). Here at File Den we take all our visitor's privacy very seriously. We will never at any point sell or transfer personal identifiable information to other companies without the visitor's consent.

**Age**  
File Den is a service not designed for users under the age of 13 (thirteen) years. If an underaged user is found using the service the user's account and any information of the user will be permanently terminated.

**Cookies and sessions**  
Cookies and sessions are data stored by your browser that contains various information that allow you to use File Den's services to their fullest. Cookies and sessions do not contain personally identifiiable information. Cookies may also be used for demographic purposes and to track various visitor patterns accross File Den.

File Den allows some third-party advertisers that advertise on our website to store cookies onto your computer. Any cookies stored by advertising companies are not covered in File Den's privacy policy. For more information please consult the privacy policy of such advertisers for more information.

Denying File Den the ability to store cookies on your computer may cause certain parts of File Den to not function correctly. We reccommend cookies are enabled to get the most out of File Den's service.

We use various third parties to deliver adverts on File Den. Some information about your visit to the site is used to determine which ads to show to you, no personal identifiable information of any form is stored.

**Information Collection**  
File Den will only ever require personally identifiable information during registration. This information is used for demographic purposes and is shared with some advertisers in order to better target adverts towards you. These companies will never send you unsolicited email.

**IP Addresses**  
Your browser sends your IP address to any website in which you visit. Your IP address may be stored in various areas of File Den's database(s) when registering or carrying out certain actions. Your IP address is stored to prevent mis-use of File Den services and for demographical purposes. 

**Information logged by File Den**  
Your browser sends various information to all websites you visit, this includes File Den. Such information includes your IP address, browser version and the page that refered you. This information is stored to prevent mis-use of File Den services. All information submitted through forms throughout the website are also logged. Only authorized personnel have access to information stored in File Den databases. Information where neccessary is also hashed or encrypted.

**Changes to this policy**  
Our policies are often reviewed and as such are subject to change. In the event of our policies being changed a notification will be displayed on the File Den website.

**Contact Us**  
For any concerns relating to this privacy policy please send an email to us using [this contact form](http://fileden.com/forums/sendmessage.php).
